{
    "true_false": [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "Computers can program themselves.",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 2,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "Java is an OOP language.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 3,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "C is an OOP language",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 4,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "SQL is used to communicate with a database.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "id" : 5,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "HTML, CSS, and Python are the three fundamental languages for front end web development",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 6,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "Pseudocode uses exact programming language syntax to represent a module in the larger program.",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 7,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "Pseudocode can be used to represent algorithms of programs.",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 8,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "A boolean represents true/false",
            "correctAnswer": "True",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 9,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "Java does not have automatic garbage collection",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 10,
            "questionType": "true_false",
            "questionText": "A linked list is not a data structure",
            "correctAnswer": "False",
            "options" : [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}